Searching for a Serial Killer: The Regina Smith Story is a
thriller, tv movie, drama film directed by Wendy Ord.
A single mother determined to provide a safer world for her
daughter, Regina joins the Dallas Police Department.
As a rookie, Regina and her partner Eddie stumble upon the first victim of what would be many murders of female prostitutes by the
notorious serial killer, whom the media dubbed “The Eyeball Killer,” because he surgically removed the eyes of his victims.
Despite only being months into the job and a woman in a profession dominated
by men, Regina risks everything to get involved in the case.
She discovers crucial evidence missed by FBI and city homicide
detectives that lands her on the doorstep of a satanic killer.
Regina Smith, played by Karrueche Tran.
Eddie, played by Blair Penner.
Charles Albright, played by Ted Cole.
Norm, played by Christopher Russell.
Detective Silva, played by Roark Critchlow.
Charles Frederick Albright (August 10, 1933 – August 22, 2020) was an American
murderer and suspected serial killer known as the Eyeball Killer.
He was charged with the murders of four women (Rhonda Bowie, Mary Lou Pratt, Susan Peterson,
and Shirley Williams) who were killed between 1988 and 1991 in Dallas, Texas.
He was only convicted of one murder and charges in the other cases were dropped due to
lack of evidence, although he is still considered the prime suspect.
The nickname "Eyeball Killer" was adopted since some of the
victims were found with their eyes removed.
Albright was incarcerated in the John Montford Psychiatric
Unit in Lubbock, Texas, until his death in 2020.
The tone is emotional and intense.